[META] timeline_id=child_safety_day_v1 mode=rtsp24h slots=8640 events=150 clip_seconds=10 slots_sha1=a5d14b71dd63151445f01a043c3cd0544c80a990 generated=2026-08-21T16:00:25
#2358 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#2394 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#2430 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#2466 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#2502 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#2538 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#2574 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#2610 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#2646 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#2682 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#2718 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#2754 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#2790 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#2826 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#2862 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#2898 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#2934 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#2970 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#3006 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#3042 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#3078 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#3114 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#3150 [CLIMB] Child climbing a chair to reach the window sill
#3186 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#3222 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#3258 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#3294 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#3330 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#3366 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#3402 [KNIFE] Child handling scissors and cutting paper
#3438 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#3474 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#3510 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#3546 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#3582 [CLIMB] Child standing on the window sill holding the frame
#3618 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#3654 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#3690 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#3726 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#3762 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#3798 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#3834 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#3870 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#3906 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#3942 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#3978 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#4014 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#4050 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#4086 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#4122 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#4158 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#4194 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#4230 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#4266 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#4302 [CLIMB] Child on the window sill pushing the casement open
#4338 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#4374 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#4410 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#4446 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#4482 [FALL] Child tripping and falling onto the floor
#4518 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#4554 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#4590 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#4626 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#4662 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#4698 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#4734 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#4770 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#4806 [CLIMB] Child climbing a chair to reach the window sill
#4842 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#4878 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#4914 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#4950 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#4986 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#5022 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5058 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#5094 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5130 [KNIFE] Child handling scissors and cutting paper
#5166 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5202 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#5238 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5274 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#5310 [CLIMB] Child standing on the window sill holding the frame
#5346 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5382 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#5418 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#5454 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5490 [CLIMB] Child climbing a chair to reach the window sill
#5526 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#5562 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5598 [KNIFE] Child handling scissors and cutting paper
#5634 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#5670 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5706 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#5742 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#5778 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5814 [CLIMB] Child standing on the window sill holding the frame
#5850 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#5886 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#5922 [KNIFE] Child handling scissors and cutting paper
#5958 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#5994 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#6030 [CLIMB] Child on the window sill pushing the casement open
#6066 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#6102 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#6138 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#6174 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#6210 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#6246 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#6282 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#6318 [FALL] Child tripping and falling onto the floor
#6354 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#6390 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#6426 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#6462 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#6498 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#6534 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#6570 [FIRE] Child playing with a lighter near the curtain
#6606 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#6642 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#6678 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#6714 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#6750 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#6786 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#6822 [CLIMB] Child climbing a chair to reach the window sill
#6858 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#6894 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#6930 [FIRE] Child playing with a lighter near the curtain
#6966 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#7002 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#7038 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#7074 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#7110 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#7146 [SAFE] Child eating at the dining table with a spoon
#7182 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#7218 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#7254 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#7290 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#7326 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#7362 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#7398 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#7434 [FALL] Child tripping and falling onto the floor
#7470 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#7506 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#7542 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#7578 [JUMP] Child jumping on the sofa back
#7614 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#7650 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks
#7686 [SAFE] Child reading a book on the sofa
#7722 [SAFE] Child sitting on the rug playing with building blocks